A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981, RG 33 FA1503
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981; 33; 276.7 Cubic Feet 725 document boxes
  - Rockefeller Family, 1962-1981 (Bulk: 1977-1981); 1977-1981; 25; 75.57 Cubic Feet 198 containers
    - Laurance S. Rockefeller (and family), 7
      - Property - Woodstock - Hagan (Box 710, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Lynch, Bryan J. (Box 711, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - The Mansion (Box 711, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Memos (Box 711, Folder 3, Box 712, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Gale House (Box 712, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Simon Pearce (Box 713, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Richardson House (Box 713, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Ross House (Box 713, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Georgina Williamson (Box 713, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Winks, Robin W. (Box 713, Folder 5, Box 714, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Town of Woodstock (Box 714, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation (Box 700, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - General Correspondence (Box 700, Folder 4-5)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - A-M (Box 700, Folder 6)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - N-Z (Box 701, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Equipment (Box 701, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Finances (Box 701, Folder 3-4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Memos (Box 701, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Photos and Maps (Box 701, Folder 6)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Minutes-Meetings (Box 701, Folder 7)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Sasaki Associates (Box 702, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Sasaki Associates - Planning Study (Box 702, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Stockholders and Trustees (Box 702, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Dairy - General Correspondence (Box 702, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Dairy - Equipment (Box 702, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Dairy - Finances (Box 702, Folder 6)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Legal (Box 703, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Dairy - Legal (Box 703, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Legal (Box 703, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Dairy - Herd (Box 704, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Hastings, Scott (Box 704, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Hastings, Scott - Ben Thresher Mill (Box 704, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Trustees (Box 704, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Contributions (Box 704, Folder 6)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Finances (Box 705, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Frye, Clayton W.- Memos - Woodstock Items (Box 705, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Grants (Box 705, Folder 3-4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Minutes-Meetings (Box 705, Folder 5, Box 706, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - A-M (Box 714, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - N-Z (Box 715, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration (Box 715, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - A-Z (Box 715, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Minutes-Meetings (Box 715, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Finances (Box 716, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Dairy (Box 716, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Thresher Mill - Film (Box 716, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Dairy - Finances (Box 717, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Dairy - Memos (Box 717, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Dairy - Minutes-Meetings (Box 717, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project (Box 717, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project - A-L (Box 717, Folder 5-7)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project - M-Z (Box 718, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project - Cahill Property and Dam (Box 718, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project - Finances (Box 718, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project - Hastings, Scott E. Jr. (Box 718, Folder 5, Box 719, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project - Museum (Box 719, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project - Design and Production Inc. (Box 719, Folder 3-4, Box 720, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project - Printed Matter (Box 720, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm Restoration - Vermont Folklife Project - Thresher Mill (Box 720, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Trustees (Box 721, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Contributions (Box 721, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Finances (Box 721, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Grants (Box 721, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Foundation - Minutes-Meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 721, Folder 5-6)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - A-Z (Box 706, Folder 3-4, Box 722, Folder 1-3)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Appreciation (Box 706, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Barton, Robert S. (Box 707, Folder 1, Box 722, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Barton Reports (Box 707, Folder 2, Box 723, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Clippings (Box 707, Folder 3, Box 723, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Contributions (Box 723, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Memos (Box 707, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Underground Distribution Lines (Box 707, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Budget-Finances (Box 707, Folder 6, Box 708, Folder 1-4)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Finances (Box 723, Folder 4-5, Box 724, Folder 1-3)
      - Property - Woodstock Inn - Printed Material (Box 724, Folder 4)
      - Radio/TV (Box 524, Folder 1)
      - Schedules (Box 524, Folder 2)
      - Squaw Valley (Box 524, Folder 3-4, Box 525, Folder 1-2)
      - Subscriptions (Box 525, Folder 3)
      - Trips (Box 525, Folder 4)
      - Trips - Europe 1980 (Box 526, Folder 1)
      - Trips - Europe 1979 (Box 526, Folder 2-4)
      - Trips - Greece (Box 526, Folder 5)
      - Trips - Grand Cayman 1979 (Box 527, Folder 1-2)
      - Trips - Japan (Box 527, Folder 3-4)
      - Trips - Nile (Cancelled) 1980 (Box 527, Folder 5, Box 528, Folder 1)
      - Trips - Spain 1976-1977, 1976 December-1977 January (Box 528, Folder 2-3)
      - Trips - Union Pacific - Seattle to Omaha 1979 (Box 528, Folder 4)
      - Trips - Union Pacific 1979 (Box 529, Folder 1)
      - Works of Art - A-Q (Box 529, Folder 2-3)
      - Works of Art - R-Z (Box 530, Folder 1-3)
      - Works of Art - Sotheby Parke Bernet (Box 530, Folder 4)
      - Works of Art - Printed Matter (Box 530, Folder 5, Box 531, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French (Box 531, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Addresses (Box 531, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Awards (Box 531, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Gifts (Box 531, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Photos - Karsh, Yousuf (Box 531, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Property (Box 531, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Property - Billings Farm (Box 531, Folder 8)
      - Chasin, Laura S. Rockefeller (Box 451, Folder 2-3)
      - Chasin, Dana James (Box 451, Folder 4)
        Biographical / Historical
      - Chasin, Alexandra (Box 451, Folder 5)
      - Case, Peter Rockefeller (Box 451, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Laurance, (Larry) (Box 511, Folder 3)
      - Waletzky, Jeremy P. (Dr. and Mrs.) Lucy R. Hamlin - The Genesis Fund (Box 608, Folder 11-12)
      - Weber, Warren T. (Mr. and Mrs.) Marion F. Rockefeller (Box 608, Folder 13)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller (and family), 8
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - A-C (Box 533, Folder 1-4)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - D-K (Box 534, Folder 1-4)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - L-Q (Box 535, Folder 1-4)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - R-Z (Box 536, Folder 1-3)
      - Addresses-Remarks - A-Z (Box 537, Folder 1-3)
      - Addresses-Remarks - Miscellaneous (Box 538, Folder 1)
      - Addresses-Remarks - United States Government - Senate Finance Committee (Box 538, Folder 2)
      - Addresses-Remarks - United States Government - Vice Presidency (Box 538, Folder 3)
      - Articles - A-N (Box 538, Folder 4-5)
      - Articles - O-Z (Box 539, Folder 1)
      - Autographs (Box 539, Folder 2)
      - Automobiles (Box 539, Folder 3)
      - Awards-Tributes - A-R (Box 539, Folder 4)
      - Awards-Tributes - S-Z (Box 540, Folder 1-2)
      - Awards - Council for the Arts in Westchester (Box 540, Folder 3)
      - Awards - Harry S. Truman Good Neighbor Award (Box 540, Folder 4)
      - Biography (Box 540, Folder 5)
      - Birthday 1978 - A-Z (Box 541, Folder 1-2)
      - Birthday Party 1978 - A-Z, 1978 May 27 (Box 541, Folder 3-4)
      - Birthday Party 1978, 1978 May 27 (Box 532, Folder 5)
      - Birthday Party 1978 - Appreciation, 1978 May 27 (Box 542, Folder 1)
      - Birthday Party 1978 - Declinations, 1978 May 27 (Box 542, Folder 2)
      - Birthday 1977 - A-Z (Box 542, Folder 3-4)
      - Boats (Box 542, Folder 5)
      - Books (Box 542, Folder 6)
      - Braden, Thomas W. (Box 542, Folder 7)
      - Christmas Gifts Acknowledged, 1978 (Box 543, Folder 1)
      - Christmas Cards - General 1978 (Box 543, Folder 2)
      - Christmas Cards Received 1978 - A-C (Box 543, Folder 3-5)
      - Christmas Cards Received 1978 - D-I (Box 544, Folder 1-4)
      - Christmas Cards Received 1978 - J-Q (Box 544, Folder 1-4)
      - Christmas Cards Received 1978 - R-Z (Box 546, Folder 1-5)
      - Christmas Cards Sent 1978 (Box 546, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Gifts Received 1978 (Box 546, Folder 7)
      - Christmas Card List 1977 (Box 547, Folder 1)
      - Christmas Cards Received 1977 (Box 547, Folder 2)
      - Christmas Gifts Received 1977 (Box 547, Folder 3-4)
      - Consultants (Box 547, Folder 5)
      - Dinners-Luncheons - A-Z (Box 547, Folder 6-7)
      - Dinners-Luncheons - Kissinger Party, 1974 (Box 548, Folder 1)
      - Dinners-Luncheons - United Nations, 1977 (Box 548, Folder 2)
      - Dyslexia - A-K (Box 548, Folder 3)
      - Dyslexia - L-Z (Box 549, Folder 1-2)
      - Employees - Marshack, Megan (Box 549, Folder 3-4)
      - Death (Box 549, Folder 5)
      - Death - Clippings (Box 549, Folder 6)
      - Death - Condolences - General Correspondence (Box 549, Folder 7)
      - Death - Condolences - A (Box 550, Folder 1-7)
      - Death - Condolences - BA-BL (Box 551, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - BM-BZ (Box 552, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - CA-CI (Box 553, Folder 1-5)
      - Death - Condolences - CJ-CZ (Box 554, Folder 1-3)
      - Death - Condolences - DA-DO (Box 555, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - DP-FL (Box 556, Folder 1-5)
      - Death - Condolences - FM-GH (Box 557, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - GI-HAM (Box 558, Folder 1-5)
      - Death - Condolences - HAN-HOP (Box 559, Folder 1-3)
      - Death - Condolences - HOR-JZ (Box 560, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - K (Box 561, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - L-LO (Box 562, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - LO-MB (Box 563, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - MCA-MK (Box 564, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - ML-N (Box 565, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - N-PA (Box 566, Folder 1-3)
      - Death - Condolences - PB-PZ (Box 567, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - Q-RN (Box 568, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - RO-SB (Box 569, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - SC-SIR (Box 570, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - SIS-SZ (Box 571, Folder 1-5)
      - Death - Condolences - T-V (Box 572, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - V-WN (Box 573, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - WO-Z (Box 574, Folder 1-2)
      - Death - Memorial Service (Box 574, Folder 3-4)
      - Death - Memorial Service - Attendees (Box 575, Folder 1)
      - Death - Memorial Service - Attendees - Foreign Diplomats (Box 575, Folder 2)
      - Death - Memorial Service - Invitation Lists (Box 575, Folder 3)
      - Death - Memorial Service - Invitees, Requests (Box 575, Folder 4)
      - Death - Memorial Service - Invitees, Requests (Box 576, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Confidential material
      - Estate (Box 576, Folder 2)
      - Estate - Executor's Meetings (Box 576, Folder 3)
      - Death - Press Releases (Box 577, Folder 1)
      - Death - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Letters of Appreciation (Box 577, Folder 2)
      - Finances (Box 577, Folder 3)
      - Furnishings (Box 577, Folder 4)
      - Gifts (Box 577, Folder 5)
      - Giving Program (Box 577, Folder 6)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection (Box 577, Folder 7)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - A-B (Box 577, Folder 8)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - C-Z (Box 578, Folder 1-3)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Articles (Box 579, Folder 1)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Bleecker, Samuel (Box 579, Folder 2-3)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Books - Masterpieces of the 20th Century (Box 579, Folder 4)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Books - Masterpieces of Primitive Art (Box 579, Folder 5)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Catalogue (Box 579, Folder 6)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Catalogue - Requests - A-G (Box 580, Folder 1-5)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Catalogue - Requests - H-N (Box 581, Folder 1-4)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Catalogue - Requests - O-Z (Box 582, Folder 1-4)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Consultants (Box 582, Folder 5)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Finances (Box 582, Folder 6)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - New Talent Club (Box 583, Folder 1)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Promotion (Box 583, Folder 2)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Radio-TV (Box 583, Folder 3)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Sale (Box 583, Folder 4)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Sale - Trenchfield Management Services Ltd. (Box 583, Folder 5)
      - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Publications, Inc. (Box 583, Folder 6)
      - Investments - Sarabam Corp. (Box 583, Folder 7)
      - Investments - Sarabam NV - Correspondence (Box 583, Folder 8)
      - Investments - Sarabam NV - Articles of Incorporation (Box 583, Folder 9)
      - Investments - Sarabam - Corporate Record File (Box 583, Folder 10)
      - Investments - Sarabam - Corporate Structure (Box 583, Folder 11)
      - Investments - Sarabam NV - Finances (Box 584, Folder 1)
      - Investments - Sarabam - Finances, 1977 (Box 584, Folder 2)
      - Investments - Sarabam - Kuwait Agreement (Box 584, Folder 3)
      - Investments - Sarabam - Lease (Box 584, Folder 4)
      - Investments - Sarabam NV - List of Participants (Box 584, Folder 5)
      - Investments - Sarabam - Meetings-Minutes (Box 584, Folder 6)
      - Investments - Sarabam NV - Minutes of Management Meetings-Voting Agreement-Non Voting Agreement (Box 584, Folder 7)
      - Investments - Sarabam - Newsclips (Box 584, Folder 8)
      - Investments - Sarabam - Notes (Box 584, Folder 9)
      - Investments - Sarabam - Proposals (Box 584, Folder 10)
      - Invitations - A-R (Box 585, Folder 1-5)
      - Invitations - S-Z (Box 586, Folder 1-2)
      - Invitations to Speak - A-E (Box 586, Folder 3-4)
      - Invitations to Speak - F-N (Box 587, Folder 1-4)
      - Invitations to Speak - O-Z (Box 588, Folder 1-5)
      - Jewelry (Box 589, Folder 1)
      - Kissinger, Henry (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box 589, Folder 2)
      - Memorials (Box 589, Folder 3)
      - Personal Services (Box 589, Folder 4)
      - Photos - A-N (Box 589, Folder 5-6)
      - Photos - N-Z (Box 590, Folder 1)
      - Politics (Box 590, Folder 2)
      - Property - NARFARMS (Box 590, Folder 3)
      - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro (Box 590, Folder 4)
      - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Photographs - Hacienda and Chapel (Box 590, Folder 5)
      - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Sale (Box 590, Folder 6)
      - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - A-H (Box 590, Folder 7)
      - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - I-Z (Box 591, Folder 1)
      - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Universidad Metropolitana (Box 591, Folder 2)
      - Property - Michigan Hill (Box 591, Folder 3)
      - Personal (Box 592, Folder 1)
      - Legal (Box 592, Folder 2)
      - Property - NARFARMS - Legal (Box 592, Folder 3)
      - Property - 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 592, Folder 4)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 592, Folder 5)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - A-P (Box 592, Folder 6)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - Q-Z (Box 593, Folder 1)
      - Property - Seal Harbor (Box 593, Folder 2)
      - Property - Seal Harbor - Sale (Box 593, Folder 3)
      - Property - Texas - Index of Correspondence (Box 593, Folder 4)
      - Property - Texas (Box 593, Folder 5-6, Box 594, Folder 1)
      - Property - Texas - Construction (Box 594, Folder 2)
      - Property - Texas - Blueprints and Maps (Box 594, Folder 3-4)
      - Property - Texas - Durham, Albert (Beto) (Box 595, Folder 1)
      - Property - Texas - East, Alice (Mrs. T.T.) Robert Thomas (Box 595, Folder 2)
      - Property - Texas - Equipment (Box 595, Folder 3)
      - Property - Texas - Finances (Box 595, Folder 4-5)
      - Property - Texas - Furnishings (Box 595, Folder 6)
      - Property - Texas - Game Preserve (Box 595, Folder 7, Box 596, Folder 1-4, Box 597, Folder 1)
      - Property - Texas - Legal (Box 597, Folder 2)
      - Property - Texas - Notes (Box 597, Folder 3)
      - Property - Texas - Ogden, Peter K. (Roberts and Roberts) - Correspondence and Expenses (Box 597, Folder 4)
      - Property - Texas - Photos-Snapshots (Box 598, Folder 1)
      - Property - Texas - Port Mansfield Airport Proposal (Box 598, Folder 2)
      - Property - Texas - Willacy County Navigation District Real Estate Potential (Box 598, Folder 3-4)
      - Property - Texas - Utilities (Box 598, Folder 5)
      - Property - Texas - Iturria, Frank (Box 599, Folder 1)
      - Property - 2500 Foxhall Road (Box 599, Folder 2)
      - Property - 2500 Foxhall Road - Sale (Box 599, Folder 3)
      - Purchases (Box 600, Folder 1)
      - Radio-TV (Box 600, Folder 2)
      - Schedules (Box 600, Folder 3-4)
      - Staff (Box 600, Folder 5)
      - Smith. Bert (Box 601, Folder 1)
      - Trips (Box 601, Folder 2)
      - Trips, France-Turkey, Saudi Arabia, Kuwait, Pakistan, Afghanistan, India and Switzerland, 1978 April-May (Box 601, Folder 3-4, Box 602, Folder 1-2)
      - Trips - France-Iran, 1977 October (Box 602, Folder 3)
      - Trips - Middle East, 1977 (Box 602, Folder 4)
      - Trusts (Box 608, Folder 4)
      - U.S. Government - Coordination of Inter-American Affairs (Box 602, Folder 5)
      - U.S. Government - President's Advisory Committee on Government Organization (Box 602, Folder 6)
      - Works of Art - A-Z (Box 603, Folder 1-3)
      - Works of Art - Sotheby Park Bernet (Box 603, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - A-O (Box 604, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - P-Z (Box 605, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - Articles (Box 605, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - Dinners-Luncheons (Box 605, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - Gifts (Box 605, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - Invitations (Box 605, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - Invitations to Speak (Box 605, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - Trips (Box 605, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - Trips - Europe 1979 (Box 606, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - Trips with Children (Box 607, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - Works of Art (Box 606, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Mary Clark (Box 606, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Rodman C. (Box 606, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Barbara (Box 606, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson, Jr. (Box 607, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson, Jr. - Trusts - Knickerbocker Club (Box 607, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Peter C. (Box 607, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Steven C. (Box 607, Folder 8)
      - Rockefeller, Dori (Box 608, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Stephen C. - Giving Program (Box 607, Folder 9)
      - Rockefeller, Steven C., Jr. (Box 608, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Stuart A. (Box 608, Folder 3)
      - Strawbridge, Geodfrey T. (Box 608, Folder 8)
      - Strawbridge, Michael R. (Box 608, Folder 9)
      - Strawbridge, Sabrina (Box 608, Folder 10)
      - Morgan, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas B. Morgan (Box 458, Folder 1)
      - Murphy, Carol (Box 458, Folder 2)
      - Murphy, James B II (Box 458, Folder 3)
      - Murphy, Malinda (Box 458, Folder 4)
      - Murphy, Malinda - Debut (Box 458, Folder 5)
      - Murphy, Margaretta H. (Wendy) (Box 458, Folder 6)
      - Pierson, Claire M. (Box 459, Folder 7)
      - Pierson, Joseph (Box 459, Folder 8)
      - Pierson, Mary Louise (Box 459, Folder 9)
      - Pierson, Rachel (Box 459, Folder 10)
      - Rasmussen, Anne Marie (Box 459, Folder 11)
      - Roberts, Ann R. (Ann Rockefeller) (Box 459, Folder 12)
      - Roberts, Ann R. (Ann Rockefeller) - Giving Program (Box 459, Folder 13)
      - Rockefeller, Ingrid (Box 474, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Jennifer (Box 474, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Laura Selene (Box 511, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Mark F. (Box 532, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Meile L. (Box 532, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Michael (Box 532, Folder 3)
        Restricted - Michael Rockefeller material
      - Rockefeller, Michael S. (Box 532, Folder 4)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller (and family), 9
      - Estate - A-Z (Box 609, Folder 1-2)
      - Estate - Finances (Box 610, Folder 1-2)
      - Estate - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust (Box 610, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box 611, Folder 1)
      - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust - Grants (Box 611, Folder 2)